wearesc.com 2006-06-05

# Scout.com: Membership

**Scout.com Privacy Policy**

Thank you for visiting our site. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this site. It describes the privacy practices for Scout.com and affiliated Web sites (such as dawgman.com or packerreport.com). [Click here](http://scout.com/) for a list of Affiliates.

This policy makes clear that Scout.com or its subsidiaries could merge with or be acquired by another business entity. Should such a combination occur, you should expect that Scout.com would share some or all of your information in order to continue to provide the service.

 **Information We Collect**  
Scout.com collects information about users in a number of ways. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services. When you register as a Scout.com user, you are asked to enter your name and email address plus additional information.

We may also ask you for personal information when you [1] enter a sweepstakes, contest, or promotion, whether sponsored by us or one of our partners; [2] when you take one of our polls or fill out a marketing survey; [3] when you make a purchase of merchandise or premium content [4] when you ask to receive any of our newsletters [5] and when you sign up for services provided by our partners, including fantasy sports games, message boards and other services offered.

While you are using the Scout.com site, we may collect certain non-personally-identifiable information about you, such as the URL you just came from, the next URL you go to, what browser you are using (e.g. Netscape, Internet Explorer), the domain name of your Internet Service Provider (e.g. AOL, Earthlink), and your IP address. We also use cookiespieces of information that Web sites transfer to your computers hard drive for record-keeping purposeson some Scout.com pages to keep track of your most recent visit to our site, identify the URL youre coming from when you buy a product on our site, provide you with an online shopping cart, and to track and customize advertising served to you.

 **How We Use Your Information and What You Can Do About It**  
We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests, that we are making changes to our subscriber agreements or billing policies, to fulfill a request by you for information, to contact you about the status of your account with us (including special promotions or discounts available to account holders), or to provide you with content alerts relating to your selected team. We may use your e-mail address if you tell us that you want to receive promotional information from Scout.com or its advertisers.

Scout.com uses the information collected from you to better understand the demographics, interests and behavior of our collective audience or to deliver advertisements and promotions that are targeted to your interests. We do not share individual information about you with advertisers in the process.

 **Who Else Sees Your Information and What You Can Do About It**  
When you visit an Affiliate site (such as washington.scout.com), we share information we have collected about you with that Affiliate. We may share your e-mail address and other information with our Affiliates, partners or advertisers sponsoring a promotion or event.

When you sign up with our partners for services such as fantasy games, free e-mail and other services, you are providing information to the partner offering the service as well as to Scout.com. You must carefully read the privacy policy of our affiliates and the partner providing the service before deciding to take advantage of the service.

Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

We also share information about our users in the aggregate to profile our collective audience to advertisers and partners. Our partners may also share the aggregate information we provide with third parties. The information data may also be shared under confidentiality agreements with independent market research companies. We may also match your information with information provided to us by third parties under confidentiality agreements.

We may have to disclose information about you to law enforcement, other government officials or third parties in order to comply with applicable law or legal process (e.g. a court order or subpoena) or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

 **How You Can Update, Correct or Delete Your Information**  
You may go to [your membership information](https://secure.scout.com/a.z?s=143&p=5&c=7) at any time to update, correct or delete personal information or to stop receiving promotional e-mail or update your e-mail address on our promotions mailing list.

 **How Your Information Is Protected**  
Scout.com takes reasonable precautions to protect your information from loss, misuse or alteration. We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to protect sensitive information such as your credit card number and a series of firewalls to protect our internal systems. You should recognize that, while it is reported to be more secure to process credit card purchases through such systems than many other traditional means, there is no such thing as perfect security on the Internet.

 **Children Under 13  
** Our site and Affiliate sites are not designed to be used by children under 13, and we ask that children under 13 do not submit personal information to Scout.com, our Affiliates or partners.

 **General**  
This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the Scout.com.com User Agreement. Should this policy be amended in any way, changes will be posted to this page.
